1050 George Street, New Brunswick, NJ 08901

Personal Website: https://xuqingsallv.github.io/

2012207908 xuqingsally@gmail.com

Summary

Skilled biostatistical programmer with 3 years of experience providing statistical analysis support and data manipulating for clinical projects in academic and industrial areas. With a master's degree in biostatistics from Columbia University and solid skill of SAS and R software programming. Have experience in SDTM, ADaM, TFL production and validation, CRF annotation and specification updating in Clinical Phase I/II/III studies.

Education

Master of Science: Biostatistics

Columbia University, Mailman School of Public Health

New York, NY, May, 2019

Courses: Probability, Biostatistics methods, Statistical Inference, Data Science, Epidemiology, Survival Analysis, Analysis of Longitudinal, Design of Medical Experiment, Randomized Clinical Trial I, Randomized Clinical Trial II

Bachelor of Science: Biological Science

Nanjing University

Nanjing, China, Jun, 2017

Working Experience

Programmer Analyst

PPD, part of Thermo Fisher Scientific, New Jersey, NJ

Feb, 2021 – Current

- Produce and validate SDTM and ADaM datasets based on specification for Phase I/II/III Oncology studies
- Produce and validate Tables, Figures and Listings (TFL) with SAS macro, including complicate shift tables and output formats for safety and efficacy analysis
- Generate annotated Case Report Forms (CRF) based on study protocol and SDTM specification
- Quality control of unblinded masked and scrambling datasets, and help with data delivery
- Update SDTM/ADaM/TFL specification based on Study protocol and datasets
- Generate SAS macro for repeated TLF outputs

Biostatistical Programmer

Brightech International, New Jersey, NJ

Sep, 2020 - Feb, 2021

- Generate and validate ADaM datasets and TFL based on standard operating procedures and specification in a timely manner
- Perform statistics analysis such as chi-square test, t test, ANOVA, logistic regression, cox models and KM plots on clinical data in phase I/II/III according to statistical analysis plan with SAS software
- · Participant in SAS macro development and debugs, specification updates for Oncology and COVID studies

Biostatistical Analyst

Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene/ NYSPI, New York, NY

Jun, 2019 – Sep, 2020

- Write statistics analysis plan, statistics and result section, provide statistical support such as tables and charts for paper publication
- Provide data cleaning, manipulation and standardization according to mapping documents for the research data platform with SAS and SAS macro
- Do descriptive statistics, hypothesis testing, logistic regression, longitudinal analysis, survival analysis and factor analysis for clinical studies with SAS and R
- Build predictive models with machine learning methods such as clustering and random forest with R
- Consulting with clinicians and researchers with study design and results interpretation for clinical studies

Skills